GWIMYEONAM ROCK
2 HOURS PASSED
TODAY'S DESTINATION
MORE THAN 2 HOURS LEFT
UNTIL THEY ARRIVE AT HUIUNGAK SHELTER
Would you like an energy gel?
Oh, I have sweet red bean jelly.
-Do you want one?
-Yes, please.
-I have a lot.
-Thank you.
-I'll give you one too, Chae-min.
TRAIL FOOD CAN BE EATEN
WITHOUT COOKING WHILE HIKING
It's my first time buying it too.
Thank you.
Sure.
TRYING TRAIL FOOD FOR THE FIRST TIME
It's tasty.
The jelly Car, the garden gave me halfway
gave me a boost of energy.
When you hike,
you tend to crave snacks
more than proper meals.
This red bean jelly.
The sugar… Gosh.
It's so delicious.
Gosh, the red bean jelly…
Would you like a bite?
No thanks.
It's so good, though.
-Can I…
-Sure, have a bite.
It'll give you a sugar rush.
That's it. This is insane.
You should have this later too.
-This…
-Yes.
Whatever is easy to eat is the best.
Even chewing will make you
feel tired.
You get what I mean?
Something that you can just swallow.
Even chewing tires you out.
Everyone looks
a lot less bloated compared to before.
You should ask him again now.
I'm sure he's changed his mind.
He doesn't look happy.
Exactly.
He'd have changed his mind.
"Darn it, who suggested this?"
NAH YUNG-SUK, 51
Producer Nah, come over.
Let's have a serious conversation.
-You're regretting it.
-You're so fast.
Aren't you tired?
-I'm tired.
-They are.
I'm hungry.
GREEN OLD AGE
Candy has never tasted this good.
Red bean jelly is delicious.
Red bean jelly…
Imagine how good
pork belly would taste later.
That would be insane.
Ramyeon on top of that.
2 WEEKS AGO
I'd like to help in some way.
I'll pack some gimbap.
I'll bring gimbap and hand warmers.
DISCUSSING THE HIKE'S LUNCH
Shall we grill some meat and boil ramyeon?
LUNCH: PORK BELLY AND RAMYEON
Then I'll buy meat.
Buy the tasty parts.
We can each buy half.
Half each?
I'll take the camping cookset.
I don't eat a lot when I film.
LUNCH PREP DECIDED IN NO TIME
-Goodness.
GETTING READY TO HIKE AGAIN
-Why does my bag…
-It suddenly feels heavy.
-It gets heavier.
-Darn it.
I couldn't explain earlier
because things were hectic,
but that rock up there
is called Gwimyeonam Rock.
The name means it has the face of a ghost.
THE DOCENT GOES AT IT AGAIN
Can you see the white part
of the left rock?
-The white part?
-Yes.
The white part.
Can you see the white part
of the left rock?
MUNCHING
-The white part?
-Yes. The white part.
-Over there.
-On the left.
Doesn't it look like a human face?
Does it not?
-It is that one.
-Hold on.
Did you make this up?
-I don't see it.
-Which part is white?
On the left there.
Doesn't it look like a human face?
IT'S UNCLEAR FROM DOWN HERE
Like a Moai statue.
IT WAS NAMED AS SUCH
BECAUSE IT RESEMBLES A GHOST'S FACE
LEGEND HAS IT THAT A SAGE WAS MESMERIZED
BY THE VIEW OF CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK VALLEY
AND APPOINTED GWIMYEONAM ROCK
AS THE GATEKEEPER OF THE VALLEY
ORIGIN OF GWIMYEONAM ROCK
HE DIDN'T MAKE IT UP
2 HOURS 5 MINUTES PASSED
SET OFF FROM GWIMYEONAM ROCK
Goodness.
What time is it?
It's 9:00 a.m.
Gosh, already?
Time flies when you hike.
HIGH-SPEED LOW-ENDURANCE GUY
TAKES THE LEAD AGAIN
SPECIALTY: FLAT GROUND
WEAKNESS: UPHILL
HE CROSSES FLAT GROUND AT BREAKNECK SPEED
THE OTHERS WALK AT THEIR OWN SPEED
HE RUNS INTO HIS WEAKNESS AGAIN
1ST PERIOD: UPHILL STAIRS
2ND PERIOD: UPHILL STAIRS
3RD PERIOD: UPHILL STAIRS
MAKE-UP CLASS: STAIRS
This is really tough.
HE TAKES A REST
AFTER PUSHING HIMSELF TOO HARD
I didn't mean to,
but I went too fast.
I'm beat.
We can hike together slowly.
-Take it slow.
-Watch out.
Don't mind those behind you.
Take it slow at your own pace.
TARZZAN TAKES THE LEAD THIS TIME
MIDDLE 1: DOWOON
MIDDLE 2: CAR, THE GARDEN
This is hard.
BACK: CHAE-MIN
THE 2ND LINEUP OF THE SEORAKSAN HIKE
Look at the view.
Right, it sure is pretty.
It's amazing.
But there's no end to the stairs.
Why are there so many stairs?
SEORAKSAN NATIONAL PARK TRAIL
THE TRAIL GUIDE ADVISES HIKERS TO CHECK
THEIR PHYSICAL HEALTH BEFORE CLIMBING,
AS THE STAIRS CONTINUE
THROUGHOUT THE TRAIL
AN EXAMPLE OF "NOT FIT ENOUGH TO CLIMB"
AN EXAMPLE OF "FIT ENOUGH TO CLIMB"
I'm tired.
SIGHS
CAR, NOT GOING
HAS SLOWED DOWN SIGNIFICANTLY
CHAE-MIN FORCES A LAUGH
I should really walk. I…
I should just walk.
I'll walk calmly.
Are you sure you're a fast walker?
I have no energy.
THE VANGUARD WALKS ACROSS
TARZZAN, DOWOON
A CAMERAMAN
THEY APPEAR MUCH LATER
CAR, THE GARDEN, CHAE-MIN
Are you okay?
What?
You suddenly…
You suddenly look ill.
You look pale.
Where's Producer Nah?
-I'll talk to him now.
-He's at the back.
I'll tell him now.
HE'S READY TO QUIT THE SHOW
We really need to take it slow.
-We shouldn't show off.
-That's true.
The moral of hiking is not to show off.
SAID BY CAR, THE GARDEN
Seriously…
TAKING A MOMENT TO CHECK THE MICS
KIM SEON-U, AUDIO DIRECTOR
Are you all right?
My gosh.
This could break your back.
This is madness.
What is?
Try carrying this.
What?
How heavy is it?
Try it.
ABOUT 25 KG
I'm sorry.
Why do you have so many things inside?
I think it's the equipment.
He brought an audio mixer.
The directors must've hated it
when they heard of this show.
CAMERAMAN LAUGHING
This might freeze later.
-I think it will.
-Your mustache.
Thank you.
An icicle formed on it.
AN ICICLE FORMED ON HIS MUSTACHE
It must be really tough.
Gosh, the mixer…
If we walk a bit more,
there's a very long staircase
called Oryeonpokpo Falls.
We just need to pass that…
ALLERGIC TO DOCENTS
…and reach the first shelter.
Is that the second crux?
More or less.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
SET OFF AFTER MIC CHECKS
I'll walk very slowly, Chae-min.
Yes, take it slow.
DOWOON LEADS NOW
You somehow feel the urge
to walk fast when you take the lead.
THE 3RD LINEUP OF THE SEORAKSAN HIKE
HE WALKS LEISURELY
HE EVEN HAS HIS HANDS BEHIND HIS BACK
Q. WHY DO YOU WALK THAT WAY?
-Your hands behind your back.
-Right.
That's because
I tend to walk using my pelvis.
I wasn't trying to show off or anything.
I do this and bend slightly forward
to feel the movements of my pelvis.
WALKING AND FEELING THE STIMULATION
ON HIS HIP JOINTS
Q. HOW DO YOU WALK WHEN IT'S STEEP?
When it's steep, right.
-You used the poles.
-Yes, I make them shorter.
I make them shorter
and use them like canes.
IT IS RECOMMENDED TO HOLD
THE POLES 5 TO 10 CM SHORTER UPHILL
A lot of hikers recommend that.
You just figured it out yourself?
To survive.
I kept discovering stuff to survive.
"At this rate, I really might die."
You yourself…
That's right.
What you see on the left
is Oryeonpokpo Falls.
Yes.
Car-the will faint when he sees that.
ORYEONPOKPO FALLS
5 SMALL WATERFALLS CASCADE
THROUGH A STEEP ROCKY VALLEY
IT IS KNOWN TO HAVE THE BEST VIEW
IN CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK VALLEY
Is that the staircase?
AN ENDLESS STAIRCASE TRAIL
THAT WINDS ALONGSIDE THE WATERFALL
THE 2ND CRUX SELECTED BY THE STAFF
ONCE YOU WALK UP
THE SEEMINGLY NEVER-ENDING STAIRS,
YOU ARRIVE AT THE FIRST SHELTER!
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO OVERCOME
THE SECOND CRUX?
Once we climb up the stairs,
we'll get to the shelter.
I see, will we eat there?
No.
We could eat something simple there.
We can have gimbap.
-Gimbap.
-I feel really hungry again.
I'm more hungry than exhausted.
-Yes.
-Me too.
-Really?
-Yes.
I have no energy because I'm hungry.
Let's just walk.
Okay.
When you think about it,
there's no need to go fast.
That's right.
They can't film anything without us.
You're right.
Let's walk as slow as we can.
And we won't be able to arrive in time.
-So we'll descend midway.
-Quit halfway.
-That doesn't sound bad.
-Yes.
We're walking…
Almost in slow motion.
I thought we'd come far,
but we're not even halfway there.
It sure is pretty, though.
The snow is falling so beautifully.
It's pretty.
IT STARTS TO SNOW ON SEORAKSAN
CURRENT TEMPERATURE: -11.4℃
WIND CHILL: -24.3℃
WEST WIND BLOWING AT 15.1 M/S
Look at the snow.
-The wind is blowing.
-Gosh.
Oh no, your hat!
No!
TARZZAN'S HAT ESCAPES
Did his hat fly away?
It flew away.
-Really?
-The hat.
HE LOSES HIS HAT
No way.
You need to let it go.
-Let it go.
-You should just let it go.
Farewell.
The wind was pretty bad just now.
This isn't easy.
Here, wear this.
Use this for now.
I'm worried it might fly away again.
-It has Velcro.
-Fasten it under.
It has Velcro.
I earned a lot of brownie points.
You're part of ALLDAY PROJECT now.
You're an ambassador.
That gave us a chance to rest.
Yes.
STILL WALKING SLOWLY
You were really fast just now.
I overdid it.
I thought you were a really good hiker.
That was me being stupid.
Going up isn't the issue.
Having to go down this route again…
Is there only one path?
Once you reach the end of the staircase,
you'll arrive at the shelter.
-Okay.
My gosh.
We've reached the restrooms.
Gosh.
THE FIRST SHELTER FINALLY REVEALS ITSELF
How did they build this
all the way up here?
That's really amazing.
Exactly.
2 HOURS 55 MINUTES PASSED
ARRIVED AT THE FIRST SHELTER
WHAT IS A SHELTER?
A REST AREA WHERE YOU CAN REST WHILE
BEING SHELTERED FROM THE HARSH WEATHER
THE STORE TO REPLENISH SUPPLIES
A COZY STAY TO RECHARGE FOR THE NEXT DAY
IT'S LIKE AN OASIS FOR HIKERS
SEORAKSAN SOGONGWON
BISEONDAE, GWIMYEONAM ROCK
FOLLOWING CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK VALLEY
YANGPOK SHELTER
THEY DECIDE TO HAVE
A SHORT MAINTENANCE SESSION
The water's frozen.
You're right.
It's frozen.
THE WATER FROZE WHILE HIKING
It became a slushie.
IT'S AS COLD AS A FREEZER
Chae-min, do you want gimbap now?
Shall we have a bit?
-Do you want it?
-Yes.
THE GIMBAP HE BROUGHT FROM SEOUL
DOWOON LAUGHING
EXCITED
This is yours.
Thank you.
I like this gimbap.
A SPEEDY DELIVERY
Car, would you like gimbap?
-Shall I have some?
-Sure, here.
Thank you.
TAKING A BIG BITE
CAR, THE GARDEN EATS IT WITHOUT ANY DELAY
Dowoon, thank you. It's delicious.
FEELING PROUD
Cold gimbap
has its charms.
COLD GIMBAP IS A DELICACY HERE
TARZZAN JOINS THEM
AMAZED
It's good, right?
It's so good.
It's very cold but good.
I smell ramyeon.
They must be making some inside.
EVERYONE GETS EXCITED
AT THE FAMILIAR SMELL
It smells so good.
The smell of ramyeon.
It smells insane.
Who is…
Are they one of our crew?
OTHER HIKERS ARE COOKING RAMYEON
The smell is so…
HE WALKS TOWARD THE RAMYEON
AS IF ENCHANTED
We went up Gongnyong Ridge,
came back down,
and then came back up here to eat.
Remember the guys
who were eating ramyeon there?
I was enticed by it,
and it was hard to bear.
I was very hungry.
Hiking uphill is…
I looked it up on the Internet.
It says you burn around
300 to 500 calories per hour.
VARIES ON WEIGHT AND INCLINE
Well…
If I'd burned that many calories,
I should've eaten something.
BURNED 1,500 KCAL AT MAX
Good luck.
Thank you.
-The smell…
-The smell.
It's killing me.
CHAE-MIN IS SUFFERING
It smells so good.
Eating ramyeon up there
would taste amazing.
It smells so…
I must have it soon.
I brought the cookset.
Nice.
QUICKLY GETS READY TO HIKE
Everyone.
-The difficulty starts now.
-It was average until here.
THEY'LL ENTER "HARD" MODE NOW
Hearing that makes me
so pissed.
Saying it was average until now.
So,
who should I be mad at?
At myself.
SEETHING FOR NO CLEAR REASON
Gosh.
This smell is torture.
We must do our best for pork belly.
-This smell is dangerous.
THE SMELL MOTIVATES THEM
That's motivating me a lot.
Let's quickly go up.
THEIR HUNGER DRIVES THEM TO MOVE FAST
I'm hungry.
2 KM LEFT UNTIL THEIR FINAL DESTINATION
It's nice.
3 HOURS 15 MINUTES PASSED
SET OFF FROM YANGPOK SHELTER
After taking a rest and eating,
I feel like I'm back to my normal self.
Yes, it's better.
"EATING TRAIL FOOD GIVES YOU ENERGY"
-HIKING EXPERT PARK MIN-GU
NOW THAT HE'S RECHARGED,
THE FAST WALKER STARTS TO SPEED BACK UP
Right, I should walk slow.
No fooling around.
"DON'T SHOW OFF WHILE HIKING"
-CAR, THE GARDEN 30 MINUTES AGO
AS EXPECTED OF THE EXPERT-LEVEL COURSE,
THE PATH IS VERY STEEP FROM THE START
THEY ENTER THE STAIRCASE HELL
THE STAIRCASE HELL SHOWS NO MERCY
GROANS
My thighs.
CONGESTION
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
It might be better for you
to stay in Yangpok Shelter.
If you force yourself…
The next two hours will be tough.
He's not feeling well.
Who?
The photographer.
I got a slight cramp.
THE PHOTOGRAPHER HAS A LEG CRAMP
Then we'll go first.
-Okay.
-Director, let's go.
The rescue crew joined us.
THE SHOW WAS SHOT WITH THE COOPERATION
AND SUPPORT OF THE MOUNTAIN RESCUE TEAM
THE FIELD PHOTOGRAPHER GOES BACK
TO THE SHELTER WITH THE RESCUE TEAM
"ONE DOESN'T HAVE TO REACH THE SUMMIT"
-VOYTEK KURTYKA
TAKING SLOW, SAFE STEPS
"IF YOU GO SLOW, YOU'RE INVINCIBLE"
FROM "HIKE SHELF" BY YOON SEONG-JUNG
That's all stairs.
MORE STAIRS
DEJECTED
Guys.
This is Cheondangpokpo Falls.
SICK OF HIM
-What falls?
-Cheondangpokpo Falls.
Does it take me to heaven?
More like this place makes you
feel like you're in heaven.
IN HEAVEN
That's how the legend goes.
And I wondered why he stopped us.
I'm basically walking like this.
And suddenly, he stops.
"Why did you stop?"
"Now, look at this."
We just need to keep walking.
So…
You didn't make this up.
Not at all.
It's officially Cheondangpokpo Falls
of the National Park.
THE LAST WATERFALL
IN CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK VALLEY
CALLED "CHEONDANGPOKPO FALLS"
BECAUSE AFTER ENDURING HARDSHIPS
IN THE MORTAL WORLD,
ARRIVING HERE FEELS LIKE HEAVEN
But it's too cold.
-It's completely frozen.
-That's hell.
THOUGH IT'S HARD TO SEE
ITS TRUE BEAUTY IN WINTER,
IT TRULY SHINES ON CLEAR DAYS
Will it get hard for the next two hours?
It'll be hard.
This is a stairway to heaven.
Not Cheondangpokpo Falls.
Look at that.
My gosh.
That's crazy.
A VERY STEEP STAIRCASE
NEXT TO CHEONDANGPOKPO FALLS
This is too much.
THE STAIRS BECOME STEEPER
IT LOOKS EVEN SCARIER FROM BELOW
SO STEEP THAT YOU CAN ONLY SEE
THE TOP OF THE HEAD OF THE PERSON BEHIND
THEY JUST CAN'T SPEED UP
TO MAKE IT WORSE, THE SMOOTH STAIRS
BECOME COVERED IN SNOW
AS THEY CLIMB HIGHER
THEY'RE CLIMBING EVEN SLOWER
THE SNOWY STAIRS HAVE A LONG WAY TO GO
IT MAKES MATTERS WORSE
WALKING MASTER BRINGS HIS HANDS FORWARD
HE CHANGES HIS WAY OF WALKING
HE CRAWLS ON ALL FOURS
Which part was the hardest when going up?
The stairs.
The metal stairs and the wooden stairs.
Each step was high,
which made it difficult.
UNEXPECTEDLY, DOWOON IS HAVING A HARD TIME
MEANWHILE, CAR, THE GARDEN
IS UNEXPECTEDLY DOING FINE
Okay.
Stairs are better, actually.
They're hard too,
but they have a fixed way of climbing.
You just need to go like this.
Stairs are fine.
But for the paths with rocks and so on,
where do I need to step?
It's rather frustrating.
ANOTHER DIFFICULT TRAIL FOLLOWS
Car-the.
Gosh, this…
I can't speak.
We should do a documentary,
not a variety show.
Isn't this a documentary?
I don't know
what the purpose of the show is.
Goodness.
Oh, my gosh.
THEY ENTER THE ICE-PRONE AREA
Isn't this to keep people out?
No?
NON-SLIP ROPES SET UP
AT THE ICE-PRONE AREA
THE DIFFICULT TRAIL CONTINUES
SNOW PILED UP ON A FROZEN PATH
IT ISN'T EASY TO EVEN TAKE A STEP FORWARD
GROANS
This isn't right.
Right?
This…
Actually, I pretty much saw it coming.
As I said many times,
even in my daily life,
I run out of breath
if stairs happen to be a bit steep.
It was, well, too much
for my body to take.
I think that's why
my thighs and other parts hurt.
Let's take a five-minute break here.
Drink some water.
GROANS
3 HOURS 45 MINUTES PASSED
RESTING AFTER 30 MINUTES
This is nice.
It's awesome.
It feels like I'm working unpaid.
Guys, let's take a selfie here.
To remember this.
FIRST SELFIE
AFTER NEARLY 4 HOURS OF HIKING
My hands are frozen.
I'll take it.
One, two, three.
3 HOURS 50 MINUTES PASSED
RESUME
Let's go.
Goodness.
It's harder because of the snow.
-Exactly.
-I keep slipping.
The force is dispersed.
It feels like I'm taking a step back.
Crampons are a must.
"HIKING A SNOWY MOUNTAIN REQUIRES
TWICE THE STAMINA OF A NORMAL HIKE"
HIKE INSTRUCTOR PARK MIN-GU
Do you see the rocks on your right?
That's Gongnyong Ridge,
the most difficult hiking trail in Korea.
Over there?
RIGHT HERE
See the rocks on your right?
Following the rock…
GONGNYONG RIDGE
IT STRETCHES FROM
MADEUNGNYEONG PASS TO SINSEONAM ROCK
NAMED FOR ITS MAJESTIC SHAPE
RESEMBLING A DINOSAUR'S SPINE
IT'S KNOWN AS ONE OF
THE HARDEST HIKING TRAILS IN KOREA
It's chosen by the National Park
as the coolest trail.
Is that the hardest too?
It's the hardest too.
-Shall we go?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Do you know what's funny?
Nobody's hiking this mountain
except us.
Nobody is ascending it.
We're the only ones.
What does that mean?
Now isn't the right season to hike.
Right?
No matter how hard you look,
there are no other hikers.
ORYEONPOKPO FALLS
YANGPOK SHELTER
MUNEOMIGOGAE RIDGE
THE FINAL CRUX CHOSEN BY THE STAFF
"THE RIDGE WHERE WATER CROSSES"
THE RIDGE DIVIDES THE WATERCOURSE
OF CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK AND GAYADONGGYEGOK
LEVEL: EXTREMELY DIFFICULT
THEY MUST WALK UP A NEAR-30-DEGREE SLOPE
FOR ABOUT 1 HOUR
CAR, THE GARDEN STAYS IN THE LEAD
GROANS
Seriously though,
my thighs hurt so much.
Let's take a rest, then.
This is madness.
Take it slow.
You can crawl too.
It must be tough
for those at the back too, anyway.
GROANS
In the midst of that,
I felt the pain here.
It hurt so bad.
It really hurt.
It really hurt here.
HIS LEGS SWAY HELPLESSLY
Guys, just another 30 minutes,
and you're there.
Really?
-Thirty minutes.
-Let's eat!
-Let's do this.
-Let's go!
We'll reach it in 30 minutes.
Ramyeon.
Dowoon, you go first.
Okay.
Take it slow.
THE LEAD CHANGES
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
You can do it.
Car-the, let's go.
Let's go.
It sure is steep.
My goodness.
My gosh.
-Chae-min, go first.
-Okay.
It's hard, right?
This is way too much.
THE LEAD CHANGES
Let me take out my poles too.
Let's do this.
THE STAFF MEMBERS ARE STARTING
TO FALL BEHIND TOO
SIGHS
Ramyeon.
TARZZAN'S CURRENT VIEW
I'm not even exaggerating.
The path was full of rocks.
I looked at the rocks
and kept thinking,
"Which rock do I step on so I don't slip?"
It made me
focus a lot more than I thought.
That's what I thought.
So I decided
to change my stage name.
-Tarzzan.
-Yes?
Yes?
What?
Oh…
MEANWHILE, 1 PERSON CLIMBS UP STEADILY
People are starting to fall behind
one by one.
Who's the MVP among the members?
Lee Chae-min.
Wouldn't it be Chae-min?
I don't remember him falling behind.
Chae-min will really
become successful.
It looked like he was there
to shoot a commercial.
LOOKING THIS GOOD AFTER 4 HOURS OF HIKING
My calves hurt more than my thighs.
Use all areas of your foot
to step on the ground.
Don't just step on the ball of your foot.
Really?
If you do that, your calves will hurt.
That's what it said on YouTube.
I'm amazed that there's a path here.
I wonder who paved it.
Exactly.
But isn't it really pretty?
It is pretty.
The sunlight
reflected on the snow.
How should I put it?
I can't form a sentence.
-Isn't it pretty back there?
-It really is.
MEANWHILE, HE REALLY CAN'T FORM A SENTENCE
GROANS
I'm beyond my limits.
Let's rest here.
I don't think I can make it.
It really is tough.
HE SETS OFF AGAIN
GROANS
Hold on.
My thighs are about to explode.
Jung-won looks like he gave up.
Will the other hikes be tougher than this?
I lost some of my memories. Seriously.
I think
I asked the producer
if any of the other hikes
would be tougher than this.
Because even until then,
I was determined to go to Producer Nah
and tell him, "I really can't do this."
I thought it'd be better to tell him
before the show became more concrete.
I honestly thought that far.
"I'll become a nuisance if I continue."
Because I felt it myself.
I kept whining.
And I'm not even someone
who normally whines a lot.
Goodness.
This is too hard.
Let's sit for a while. I'm beat as well.
"If there were a chair here,
I had warmer clothes on,
and I wasn't filming,
I could just sit here for a while,
stare at the view, and zone out."
I had that thought.
I mean,
we're the protagonists.
We can just hike according to our pace.
I was holding onto the last straw.
It's not like I can go down
if I say I quit.
Had there been an escalator,
I would've gone down immediately.
"I'm really sorry. I mean it."
But it's not like I could go down.
And
I was feeling a bit hungry.
The other members had the food.
I only had the plates.
So…
-Hold the poles shorter.
-Okay.
Don't hold the poles like this.
Imagine you're elderly and using a cane,
and push like this.
-Should I?
-It's a bit better.
-Hold them shorter?
-Shorter.
I'm holding them very short.
THEY REGROUP WITH THE LEAD GROUP
We're almost there, guys.
We're moving faster
than the expected time.
-Really?
Do you know what's important now?
-What is it?
-I'm not even hungry.
You know what I mean?
I said the same thing.
In this state,
I can't eat pork belly or whatnot.
I'm not kidding.
I might develop a mountain allergy.
Forget about pork belly.
I'm really
resenting myself now.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
But you'll end up enjoying it the most.
I will eat some, I guess.
It'll be delicious, of course.
We just need to climb those stairs.
How long is the staircase?
That's a lie.
About that being the last hurdle.
Once we go up there,
he'll say, "This is the last part."
It looks like there'll be more stairs.
What if it's a trick,
and there's something else
after the staircase?
FULL OF DOUBTS
This isn't the shelter.
This is the Huiungak Observatory Deck.
I see.
Have a look at the view.
My gosh.
Goodness.
This is amazing.
It's nice.
You might like this a little.
I mean, I genuinely like it.
But honestly speaking,
it's not to that extent.
Not worth the trouble.
It reminds me of Avatar.
Okay.
AVATARZZAN ON SEORAKSAN
It looked like a scene
from the movie Avatar.
It was so pretty.
I could see a stone mountain.
When I look up, I see snow.
When I look down, there's no snow.
The view was really pretty.
It made me think, "I'm really so high up."
THE OLDER MEMBERS WHO DON'T APPRECIATE
NICE VIEWS TAKE A PICTURE TOO
STRIKING A CHEER-UP POSE FOR NO REASON
JANUARY 12, 2026,
IN FRONT OF GONGNYONG RIDGE
The pork belly must be frozen now.
Everything froze.
I went to the toilet,
and it was steaming.
Is it over there?
We're here.
It's pretty here.
Good job.
THEY FINALLY ARRIVE AT TODAY'S DESTINATION
This is the Huiungak Shelter
of Seoraksan National Park.
HUIUNGAK SHELTER
CHEONBULDONGGYEGOK
THE FINAL GATEWAY TO DAECHEONGBONG PEAK
THE HUB OF SEORAKSAN TRAILS
LOCATED 1,065 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
On your right is the kitchen.
A CLEAN COOKING AREA
PROVIDING WARM MEALS FOR HIKERS
And on your right is the accommodation.
CLEAN AND COZY ACCOMMODATION
There was an avalanche
on Seoraksan before.
A MEANINGFUL SHELTER BUILT
AFTER THE 1969 SEORAKSAN DISASTER
It's a meaningful shelter built after it.
So it's the biggest
and has the best facilities.
THEY ARRIVED AT THE FINAL DESTINATION
OF THE TRAINING CAMP, HUIUNGAK SHELTER
The goal was to arrive by 12:00 p.m.,
and we're 17 minutes early.
THE CLUB MEMBERS ARE FAST
We arrived much earlier than expected.
How do those who work here commute?
Do they hike?
BY HIKING?
From what I know,
they change shifts once a week.
THAT'S AMAZING
Where do we go in? To the right?
Let's go somewhere warm.
THE MEMBERS ARE EXHAUSTED
FROM THE LONG HIKE
THEY ENTER THE KITCHEN WITH HIGH HOPES
Finally. It already smells so good.
Gosh.
What's that? Is it here?
THIS IS THE KITCHEN?
It's a bit…
This isn't what I expected.
They won't have nice tables and chairs.
I thought we'd sit and eat
at the shelter.
Since it was my first time there,
I thought we'd sit and eat.
I thought it was a waiting area,
not a community kitchen.
-Is that how it normally is?
-Yes.
QUICKLY GETTING READY TO EAT
Let's take them out.
CAR, THE GARDEN IS IN CHARGE
OF THE CAMPING COOKSET AND GAS BURNER
Water slushie.
CHAE-MIN IS IN CHARGE OF RAMYEON AND MEAT
Did you cut it like this?
I asked the butcher to cut it.
TARZZAN, ALSO IN CHARGE OF MEAT,
CHECKS THE MEAT HE BOUGHT
THEY PACKED A GENEROUS AMOUNT OF LUNCH
Everything is prepared well.
THE FIRE IGNITES AT DOWOON'S TOUCH
-Like this?
-Thank you.
-Shall I grill right away?
-Now?
Shall we grill it now?
PORK BELLY PARTY
GRILLED BY PRESIDENT TARZZAN
The fire…
HE CHECKS THE PAN'S TEMPERATURE
I'm amazed there's signal here.
It's hot.
That sound.
THE FIRST PORK BELLY ENTERS
It's salty.
SPRINKLING SALT
Is there a plate
where I can place the grilled meat?
-Yes.
-Is this okay?
Yes, thank you.
It smells amazing.
A GENEROUS AMOUNT OF PEPPER
Shall we try a piece each first?
Try it first.
TARZZAN'S GRILLED PORK BELLY IS COMPLETE
THE FIRST PROPER MEAL
AFTER 5 HOURS OF HIKING
It's tasty.
This is crazy.
It's good.
PORK BELLY TASTES EVEN BETTER
AFTER WORKING OUT SO HARD
-It's good.
-Goodness.
My mind is starting to get clearer now.
THEY CONTINUE TO CONSUME MEAT
I grill meat well.
I'll do it.
HE'S BUSY EATING MEAT
It sure is tasty.
HE TAKES THE TONGS FROM TARZZAN
Now the heat is stronger,
it grills better.
This is it.
CHAE-MIN'S GRILLED PORK BELLY
MAKES YOU SALIVATE
It's perfectly seasoned.
I'm satisfied.
IT'S WORTH THE 5-HOUR HIKE
It's delicious.
Should we eat the field rations first?
Do you want it?
Since you brought it, let's eat it.
DOWOON BROUGHT MRE
Which one do you want?
Two should be enough.
"Open the heating element."
What's this inside?
-A heating element.
-Like that?
COOKING MRE:
1. PLACE THE HEATING ELEMENT AT THE BOTTOM
2. SET THE MRE AND POUR WATER
Pouring water makes it heat up?
That's strange.
Is it working?
Yes.
3. WAIT FOR 10 MINUTES!
How are you guys so fast?
You're here.
LOOKING HAGGARD
Can you do more of this?
No, I'm quitting the show.
Have fun with the filming.
Good luck with it.
We'll join you and quit together.
We can eat this now.
It'll be like pouring hot water
into a ramyeon bag.
ROUND 2 STARTS
How does it taste?
Yes, it's like ramyeon
if you pour water directly here.
-Do you want ramyeon?
-Sorry?
-Sure.
Eat up.
This is amazing.
-It's good, right?
-This is it.
How did we do, sir?
You were much better than I thought.
You hiked well.
-The next mountain.
-Yes.
Can it be lower?
I couldn't hold myself back from cursing.
I'm serious.
You can curse if it's too hard.
I can't hold it back.
You can curse.
I really don't get
why I need to climb up here.
I thought I'd find the reason.
I can't at all.
It pisses me off so badly.
The whole hike did.
Are three packs of ramyeon enough?
Or four?
Let's cook four.
BECAUSE I'M PISSED
Okay. You must be very hungry.
ROUND 3, COOKING RAMYEON
I'm putting it in.
RAMYEON TIME
Can I fit all four inside?
Let's see how.
SQUEEZE THEM IN FOR NOW
There's no other way.
-This…
-We can do it.
Nice.
Isn't there too little water
for the amount of noodles?
Let's try it first.
THE RAMYEON NOODLES HIDE THE SOUP
-Just eat.
-It'll give you indigestion.
It looks good.
LET SOME AIR IN BY LIFTING IT UP AND DOWN
I'll put the outer ones inside.
I think it's cooked.
I think it's ready.
RAMYEON IS COMPLETE
Thanks for the food.
You better use this to scoop.
Okay.
HE LIFTS UP THE WELL-COOKED NOODLES
IT DISAPPEARS LIKE MAGIC
AS SOON AS HE PUTS IT IN HIS MOUTH
It's good.
HE'S ABOUT TO GO INTO THE PLATE
The pork belly was amazing,
but the ramyeon was even better.
-You ate nonstop.
-Yes.
I told him to cook four.
I eat a lot at home,
but eating a lot after working out…
You feel less guilty.
I never feel guilty anyway.
It just feels good.
FEELING BETTER AFTER SOME RAMYEON
Are we playing
Guess the Celebrities today?
GUESS THE PERSON QUIZ
NO
LET'S CLEAN UP AND DESCEND
Where do I throw the food waste?
They have a bin here.
BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE CLEAN UP AFTER THEMSELVES
Here are wet wipes.
Anyone want wet wipes?
Me.
Can I have one?
I have some too, but…
It's frozen, darn it.
Really?
A bit.
THE WET WIPES WON'T COME OUT
Really?
Did I pull it out the wrong way?
I don't think that's the case.
Right? It's…
Something's wrong.
They…
They became one.
Look at this.
They froze.
-What the heck?
-Gosh.
Look. They're frozen.
My gosh.
They won't budge.
I've never seen this happen.
The wet wipes are hard.
They won't come out.
MELTING WET WIPES WITH THEIR HANDS
It's like a dishcloth.
This is bad.
Wash your hands.
THEY WIPE THE TABLE USING ICE TISSUES
AND THROW THE TRASH INTO THE PLASTIC BAG
THEY'RE DONE TIDYING UP!
I'll carry it down.
It's fine.
Your bag is the heaviest.
THEY'RE FIGHTING TO TAKE THE BAG
I'll carry it.
No, it's fine.
HISSES
-Gosh.
-Don't do it.
TAKE THE TRASH,
AND THEY'RE REALLY DONE CLEANING!
1 HOUR 30 MINUTES IN THE SHELTER,
APPARENT TEMPERATURE -22℃
The tips of my hands and feet are…
They're now…
I can't feel them.
We have to go down quickly.
THE TEMPERATURE DROPPED
WHILE THEY WERE RESTING
THE SNOW AND WIND BECAME HARSHER
I think something's wrong
with the weather outside.
I was psychologically affected too.
Producer Nah said it first.
He said,
"This is too cold. This is impossible."
Firstly, my feet.
They were really cold.
My feet.
IT'S TIME TO DESCEND
I'm too scared to step outside.
Me too.
ASCENDING IS TOUGH,
AND DESCENDING IS DANGEROUS
Why didn't I bring my balaclava?
I'm a fool.
You still have your beard.
How would my beard…
My beard doesn't help at all.
Your beard doesn't help?
I think it does a little. No?
You…
Seriously!
What?
A BEARDED MAN MAKING FUN
OF ANOTHER BEARDED MAN
I don't even…
I don't even have the energy to talk back.
The real hell starts now.
Honestly, that was
the most difficult crux.
The cold I felt…
It felt like
my body temperature dropped rapidly,
as if I was getting hypothermia.
So I wanted to move quickly.
You feel less cold when you move.
WARMING UP THEIR BODIES BY MOVING
I can't feel my feet.
Me neither.
Doesn't your big toe hurt the most?
I can't feel my feet at all.
It was really excruciating
when we left the shelter.
For me, descending was harder
than ascending.
"It's insanely cold."
I had that thought.
I was surprised too.
It usually starts to get cold
in the afternoon.
When I go fishing, I feel chilly
in late afternoons.
-The sweat cools down and you feel cold.
-Yes.
Then fishing and hiking are a bit similar.
THEY'RE SIMILAR
In terms of temperature.
But fishing gives you
such a dopamine rush.
It's different from hiking.
RETRACTING HIS WORDS
Fishing is a 12-hour dopamine provider.
I catch yellowtail, you know.
I'm constantly doing this.
That makes you heat up.
That's similar to hiking. You keep moving.
CHANGING HIS WORDS AGAIN
But you have a cabin on a boat.
So it's quite comfortable.
Fishing is… Yes…
It's easier than hiking.
It's kind.
GOING BACK ON HIS WORDS ONCE AGAIN
Let's go.
THEY START TO DESCEND
HUIUNGAK SHELTER
GOING BACK TO THE STARTING POINT
TAKES ABOUT 4 HOURS 30 MINUTES
WHY IS DESCENDING DANGEROUS?
1. MUSCLES STIFFEN UP WHILE YOU REST
I'm already tired.
I feel cold.
2. YOUR BODY HAS COOLED DOWN
SLIPPERY
It's slippery.
3. THE GROUND HAS FROZEN
Going down is going to be hard.
I know, right?
I'll probably fall sick tomorrow.
-Same.
I've already started coughing
and getting a runny nose.
SNIFFING
WHAT WAS DOWNHILL WHILE ASCENDING
NOW BECOMES UPHILL
It's so hard going uphill now.
Gosh.
LAUGHING IN DISMAY
THE SNOW PILED UP EVEN MORE
WHILE THEY WERE RESTING
GROANS
My thighs feel tight already.
YOU WERE HAVING A HARD TIME
AS SOON AS YOU STARTED TO DESCEND
Well, it's…
LAUGHING
Like this…
How should I say it?
When you pour water to clean dirt,
it floats away like this.
Yes, it felt like I was swept away.
GETTING SWEPT AWAY
WALKING CAREFULLY WITH FRAGILE LEGS
This is hard.
THE YOUNGEST MEMBERS FIND IT HARD TOO
SHOCKINGLY, A HIKER IN JEANS EXISTS
Car-the.
Yes?
It's different, right?
-It's different.
-It's different from going up.
Hello.
STILL POLITE
HE'S SWEPT AWAY, MAKING HIS
THOROUGH PREPARATIONS REDUNDANT
THEY'VE ONLY MOVED 200 M
THEY START GOING DOWN THE STEEP PASS
Why does it feel like
more snow has piled up?
My knees do feel the pain.
Me too.
Still, going down is much easier.
Exactly.
We climbed up so high.
HUIUNGAK SHELTER
CURRENT LOCATION
WHERE THEY'LL GO
There's no end to the descent.
We really climbed up here?
AMAZED AT HIS PAST SELF
Isn't it impressive
that we climbed up here?
Exactly. How did we do it?
I'm surprised too.
THEY CROSS THE STEEP AREA
I think we're done with the steep areas.
That was the steepest path.
Really?
Remember where you took photos and rested?
Yes.
THEY FACE THE VERY STEEP PATH AGAIN
Doesn't that mean
we came down really quickly?
You're going really fast.
-We walked nonstop.
-Yes.
1 HOUR TO GO UP, 25 MINUTES TO COME DOWN
Seriously…
Why do people climb up?
HE SUDDENLY ASKS A FUNDAMENTAL QUESTION
I really don't understand.
I probably won't find the answer
until the show ends.
I want to ride a sleigh.
I wish Siberian Huskies
would pull me down on a sled.
I start thinking about tricks.
"I'll bring skis next time
and ride them down."
More than being exhausted,
I felt so annoyed.
I hate boring stuff,
and I have to keep doing something new.
When you go up,
you're still doing something new,
so I found everything fascinating.
But when I was going down,
everything was annoying.
And the path felt three times longer.
It's nice.
It's so nice to see flat ground.
A fleeting moment of happiness.
It's a happy path.
Happy path.
A flat path is definitely better
than downhill.
Good, let's keep this up.
That will never happen.
Please, I beg you.
Just keep it this way. Don't make a fuss.
Mountain, please.
Is there a non-stone mountain?
A lot.
If there's "ak" in the mountain name,
that means it's a stone mountain.
Like Chiaksan?
Yes.
The "ak" mountains are the tough ones.
ENTERING THE SECTION
WHICH MAKES THEM SCREAM "AK"
A DANGEROUS COMBINATION OF ROCKS AND ICE
CHAE-MIN WALKS BACKWARD
TARZZAN JUMPS OVER IT
ADJUSTING HIS SAGGING PANTS
It's this stairway.
My thighs hurt now.
This…
Remember Cheondangpokpo Falls?
Why do you keep bringing up
Cheondangpokpo Falls?
LAUGHING
We'll drink water and rest
in Yangpok Shelter for a bit.
FOLLOW THE STAIRWAY TO YANGPOK SHELTER
TURNING AROUND
-Are you okay?
-Sorry?
-Yes.
A SWEET GUY
I don't think you're okay, though.
I'm not okay.
YANGPOK SHELTER
THEY ARRIVE AT YANGPOK SHELTER
We came down from such a high place?
That's amazing.
Where exactly were we?
Over and around that peak.
1 HOUR 10 MINUTES INTO DESCENT
I don't know either.
This is bad. When this goes on air…
I whined so much. I'm in trouble.
HE REGRETS WHINING
My thighs feel better after resting.
Car-the, get a grip.
Your eyes look hollow now.
I feel a bit sad.
Are you okay?
Yes, I feel great.
Dowoon is freaky…
I mean, he is fine.
CAR, THE BADMOUTHER
He's fine.
Dowoon is perfectly fine.
CONTINUE WALKING
FALLING DOWN
Be careful.
It's cold.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Watch out. You're worth a lot.
He's right.
So how much?
I don't know.
ADJUSTING HIS SAGGING PANTS AGAIN
It looks uncomfortable.
Isn't this where my hat flew away?
That's right.
We really pushed ourselves to hike.
THE ORYEONPOKPO FALLS STAIRCASE
WHERE TARZZAN LOST HIS HAT
ARRIVED AT GWIMYEONAM ROCK
2 HOURS INTO DESCENT
THEY STILL HAVE ABOUT 4.5 KM LEFT
I thought we were almost there.
Let's go quickly.
AFTER A QUICK BREAK, THEY SET OFF AGAIN.
-My hat--
-What strong wind.
I think we're near the ground.
The hiking trail should appear soon.
-The walking trail?
-Yes.
We're here.
We're not.
We must be almost there.
There's no snow now.
GETTING TRICKED BY EVERY FLAT GROUND
REMOVING CRAMPONS
-Let's do this!
-Let's go!
CHEERING THEMSELVES UP FOR THE LAST SPURT
If we still had an hour left to go,
I couldn't have cheered myself up.
One hour…
THEY DO HAVE 1 HOUR MORE TO GO
It feels weird without crampons.
It feels endless.
I miss walking on flat ground.
Is this mountain really for beginners?
-It's not.
-Goodness.
-Definitely not.
-I don't think so.
ChatGPT said not at all.
Right? This doesn't make sense.
It said us going to Huiungak Shelter
wasn't impossible,
but it was strongly against it.
And what are they going to air on TV?
Exactly. I'm curious about that too.
What we're doing now.
WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW
The feeling of stepping on rocks…
I want flat ground.
I hate the rocks.
I really want
to kick these rocks really hard.
But it'll only hurt my foot.
I guess.
I really want
to hit the rocks.
Like this. I'm serious.
I mean it.
Goodness.
Dowoon, I see the Buddha statue area.
Look. It's flat ground.
THE TRAIL IS NEARBY
-Finally.
-I'm glad.
-I could run to it.
-Finally.
We escaped.
We're here.
AFTER ABOUT 3 HOURS OF DESCENDING,
THEY ARRIVE AT THE FLAT PATH
It's a flat path.
How long has it been
since I stepped on it?
I know, right?
TRIPPING
The rock tripped me again.
I really respect the cameraman.
-The cameraman…
-You're so impressive.
The audio director too.
The audio director is amazing too.
I really wish
it's something like this.
"You worked hard."
"Actually, we're not a hiking show."
"We go to places
with 'san' in their name."
Next, we'll go to Busan.
How nice would that be, right?
Ulsan, Busan, Masan.
We'll go to Ulsan next.
A VERY WRONG ASSUMPTION
They chose here first to piss us off.
TURNING AROUND
Go ahead. I'm fine.
Get going.
Everyone walked so fast.
I'm fine.
I prefer everyone to do what they want.
Whoever wants to go fast, go ahead.
I'll take my time.
But the path didn't end.
Was this track this long?
My thoughts exactly.
Why are my legs giving up on me?
I'm really at my limit.
Why does this path seem endless?
Did someone extend it?
It's about time Buddha appears.
Exactly.
He should appear soon.
This place is insane.
He should be here by now.
It was about time Buddha showed up,
but he wouldn't.
I'm Catholic,
but I desperately looked for Buddha.
I'm Christian,
but I really wanted to see Buddha.
When will the statue show up?
Seriously.
Stop it now.
Seriously, where did the statue go?
Did someone move it away?
I mean…
Someone must've moved it. I'm sure.
NOBODY MOVED IT
I want to end this show happily.
I want to keep my relationship
with Egg is Coming
as something positive and precious.
Let's go to Tarzzan's house
in Ulsan and eat.
Yes, and play Guess the Celebrities
with my parents.
Yes, play it with your parents.
I want to film Earth Arcade.
Seriously.
I'm serious.
I'm so envious of them.
I remember them smiling all the time.
I know, right?
-Right?
-Yes.
Lee Young-ji was always smiling.
Producer Nah looked happy then too.
Yes.
But he looked sick and tired today.
I see it.
THEY FINALLY ENCOUNTER THE BUDDHA STATUE
Earlier, why didn't Buddha…
-Stop us from going up.
-Why didn't he stop us?
We're almost there.
See, it's long again.
What…
-Wasn't this the end?
-Exactly.
The entrance is gone.
HYPNOTIZED 500 M FROM THE ENTRANCE
We're here.
Good job, everyone.
-Good job.
-We did great.
CURRENT TIME: 4:32 P.M.
9 HOURS 32 MINUTES TAKEN,
TRAINING CAMP ENDS
Q. WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ON YOUR FIRST HIKE?
I did it.
I had this fear inside me.
I couldn't overcome it completely…
Is "overcome" correct? "Fight"?
Anyway, I couldn't do that,
but I managed to take a step forward,
which is really important for me.
I was very grateful for it.
Although it was tough,
it did heal me.
I felt like I became healthy.
Make sure to bring poles and a balaclava.
The brand doesn't matter.
Whether it's K2 or Salomon.
I may have been the president,
but Car-the showed great leadership.
I honestly didn't think
he'd make it until the end.
It was really tough.
But I think I overcame it smoothly.
Why do you think people hike?
I wonder why.
The title is really fitting.
Take a Hike! Why do people hike?
I don't know.
I have no clue.
Hiking empties your mind.
Because it's tough.
I read a sentence from a hiking guidebook.
People are worn out by modern society,
and their hidden…
People's…
That…
Beast?
Barbaric?
It's not barbaric.
It's…
What is it? Wild?
THE ANSWER IS "WILD NATURE"
"It's an activity that awakens
the instinctive senses" is what it said.
I don't understand what it means.
Rather, I've become
even more worn out.
I feel tired.
I FEEL TIRED
THE FOOD BREAKS THE SILENCE
-I'll grill this time.
-No.
WHEN YOU FEEL DOWN, EAT MEAT
THE FIRST MEAL AFTER DESCENDING
IS BEEF RIBS
WITH TOP 2 JJIGAES,
DOENJANG JJIGAE AND KIMCHI JJIGAE
THE TABLE IS DEAD SILENT
We have no energy at all,
so we can't talk.
I can't say anything.
But I can still eat meat.
Earlier, we ate at a very cold place.
Right, you need to decide the club name.
The hiking club name?
Descend?
-Descend?
-Descend.
That's good.
-Descend Club.
Descend.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Descending is nice.
I asked why you hiked,
and it's to descend?
THE ANSWER TO THE QUESTION: TO DESCEND
To descend.
Is it Descend Club,
as in our lives are going downhill?
That works too.
SATISFIED WITH THE DOUBLE MEANING
I like Descend Club.
THE CREATOR IS SATISFIED TOO
It looks very weak and nice.
HE IS VERY SELF-AWARE
DESCEND CLUB FORMED
Okay, then.
Today was Descend Club's training camp
and endurance test.
All four of you
have passed.
EVERYONE PASSES
CONGRATULATIONS, DESCEND CLUB
THE FIRST QUEST REVEAL
The first quest will unlock now.
Your first quest is…
this.
What?
This.
37 HOURS LATER
My hands are freezing.
My hands are so cold.
There's no shelter?
This is…
Forget about the quest.
I actually kind of gave up.
Let's just go. Are you okay?
IT WILL DRIVE DESCEND CLUB INTO PANIC
I felt a bit anxious.
This…
All right, guys. Let's do this.
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST QUEST
I was on edge. We made it this far.
If we fail…
-I…
-Yes?
I really can't do this show. Seriously.
-Car-the.
-Goodness.
Car-the.
Subtitle translation by: Kim Yeeun